DAVANJIT SANDHU

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

An experienced software developer with 4+ years of professional experience, where applications that were developed are still in active use. Has a wide range of skills across diverse tech stacks and the ability to quickly adapt to new ones.

CONTACT

(519) 816-8130

davanjit@hotmail.com

Windsor ON, Canada

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

Minor in Political Science UNIVERSITY OF WINDSOR 2016 - 2021

KEY SKILLS

Software Development:

C, C++, C#, Lua, Java, Kotlin, Python

Web Development:

React.js, Node.js, Express.js, Next.js, HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Bootstrap.js, MSSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, Azure, Docker, Git, API's, Vite, PHP, Jest, Angular, Laravel

Android Development:

Android Studio, React Native (Expo)

Game Development:

Unity, Godot, Phaser.js, Babylon.js, PyGame, GameMaker, GameMaker 2, Love2D

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Champion Products Corp. - Windsor ON January 2022 - Present

- Created a <u>website</u> for warehouse workers that tracks employee activity and relays the information to the administrators.
- Maintained company websites and added new features.
- Mainly used React.js on the frontend and Node.js with Express.js on the backend. Also used Next.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, Bootstrap.js, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Microsoft SQL Server, Docker and hosted websites on Azure.
- Used third party API's to enhance websites with features such as adding facial recognition to the employee tracking website.
- Updated backends of websites to add new and relevant data.

Software Developer Intern

Gao Tek Inc. - Remote August 2021 – November 2021

- Worked on the protocols development team.
- Translated VoIP documents into C code.

LINKS

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/davanjit-sandhu-496200211/

GitHub

https://github.com/Dav-Sandhu

Website

https://dav-sandhu.github.io/Personal-Website/